When Napoleon led Boulogne for a year in
his fat bottom boats, and in his grand
army He was told by someone there
are bitter weeds in England.
There are certainly, a great many more of
them since the British expeditionary force
returned.
Sir I have myself full confidence that if
all do their duty, if nothing is neglected
and if the best arrangements are made
and they are being made, we shall prove
ourselves.
once more able to defend our Island home,
ride out the storm of war and to outlive
the menace of tyranny
if necessary for years.
If necessary, alone.
At any rate that is what
we are going to try to do.
That is the resolve of His Majesty's
government, every man of them.
That is the will of
parliament in the nation.
The British empire and the french republic
linked together in their cause and in
their need will defend to the death
their native soil aiding each other.
Like good comrades to the
utmost of their strength.
We shall go on to the end, we shall fight
in the france We shall fight on the seas
and oceans, we shall fight with growing
confidence and growing strength in the air
We will defend our Island,
whatever that costs may be.
We shall fight on the beaches, we
shall fight on the landing grounds.
We shall fight in fields and in the
streets, we shall fight in the hills.
We shall never surrender.
And if, which I do not for a moment
believe, this Island or a large part of
it, subjugated and starving, then our
empire beyond the seas armed and guarded
by the British fleet, will carry on the
struggle until in God's good time the new
a world with all its power and might,
steps forth to the rescue and liberation
of the old.